var questions = [{
  question: "What score did Zack get on his SATs?",
  answers: [900, 1020, 1502, 1600],
  correct: 2
}, {
  question: "What is the name of Screech's robot?",
  incorrect: ["Mike","Kevin", "Harry", "Slater"],
  correct: 1
}, {
  question: "What was Slater's football jersey number?",
  incorrect: [6, 9, 12, 11],
  correct: 0
}, {
  question: "Finish this line: \n I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so.....",
  incorrect: ["drunk", "tired", "excited", "scared"],
  correct: 3
}, {
  question: "Which is NOT a name of an employee at the Max?",
  incorrect: ['James', 'Jeff', 'Kelly', 'Bruce'],
  correct: 3
}, {
  question: "What was name of the band the group created?",
  incorrect: ['Zack Attack', 'Friends Forever', 'The Max', 'The Temptations'],
  correct: 0
}, {
  question: "What was Screech's dog's name?",
  incorrect: ['Max', 'Walter', 'Hounddog', 'Sparky'],
  correct: 2
}, {
  question: "What is Lisa's alias on the Teen Line in 1-900 Crushed?",
  incorrect: ['Jewel', 'Princess', 'Angel', 'Peaches'],
  correct: 1
}, {
  question: "What is Jessie Spano's middle name?",
  incorrect: ['Marie', 'Ann', 'Myrtle', 'Christine'],
  correct: 2
}, {
  question: "How much money did Lisa charge on her Dad's credit card?",
  incorrect: ['$394', '$375', '$342', '$386'],
  correct: 3
}];


